Life is a way of rewarding good deeds.
Often when you help others, you're helping yourself.
Run.
It's you.
Run for it before you get in my way even more.
Run.
Run the fire.
Car.
Honey.
Let's go.
infinitely the characters I saw inside their mouths were joy sorrow anger and
pleasure those four must be the most powerful versions but if they divide
any further they weaken
behind me I have to defeat it just this one then get back to Nezuko and Kenya
where'd it go when I stabbed is gone I see it can't split off any further
how do you like my talents aren't they swift aren't they sharp on top of that
they're strong enough to smash diamonds go on tremble
tremble and rejoice as your blood gushes out of every orifice
I gotcha
huh
yeah
now you've gone and done it
I have to get back and help Nezuko and Kenya but how Nezuko hang in there
come on you're doing great just one more push
what's wrong that all you got quit goofing off and dismember her Karaku
I'm getting more annoyed by the second here keep your hands to yourselves this little girl is mine for the killing you and Aisetsu can find your own prey
hey Karaku seems you're struggling let me be the one to finish her off
my spear is stuck
it seems you're struggling let me be the one to finish her off
it seems like you've forgotten your opponent is over here
why do you keep letting your guard down Aisetsu it's infuriating
you fool
damn it he's pulling it out
a slow and painful death is a sad thing to witness isn't it
oh
Ha!
I went for his vital spot so he could have a quick death,
but I guess he couldn't die with my spear still lodged in his body.
At the very least, his suffering is over now.
What's this? The Amida Sutra. How pious of you to choose that as your last words.
The man's still alive, Aizetsu! Hurry up and split his head in two!
I was just about to do that so stop yelling at me. You're making me sad.
I'll cut your damn heads off as many times as it takes! Die, you scumbags!
Crap! No matter what I do, I can't dodge this lightning!
Damn that bastard with a stab!
What's going on here? Why won't he die? Aizetsu dealt him a fatal blow, didn't he?
Gah!
Hang on a second! You look like you're having a lot more fun with him!
Gah! Gah! Gah!
You're done entertaining me, little girl!
Gah!
Sekiro! After I've ripped this girl's limbs off of her,
impale her with your staff and keep blasting her with lightning so she can't move!
That was my plan from the start, you imbecile!
imbecile what kind of ferocious kick was that what are you doing you idiot
and finish her
He's fast. Faster than before.
I have to hurry up and get back.
The building Nezuko and Genya are in is close.
How do I get there? Think!
That's it. If I can't bring the demon down here...
But wait. I might just end up making matters worse.
What do I do? What do I do?
I have to do it! I don't have any other options!
Nezuko! Genya! Don't die. I'll be there soon.
Did you finally decide to die?
Why won't you give up already?
What is this? Who the hell are you anyway?
What are you?
You really want to know?
My name is Genya Shinazukawa.
And don't you ever forget it!
Because that's the name of the man.
Who is going to kill you!
The building they're in should be just over there!
If I pull this off, I'll be there in a flash!
Don't misjudge the direction.
Use the demon's momentum and ability to fly!
To get there quickly and save Nezuko and Genya!
Making her run for it?
You're all out of energy now!
I knew it!
He's light!
Otherwise he wouldn't be able to fly!
Not with wings this size!
I can make it!
Nezuko! Genya!
First Karaku, now even Uroki!
What the hell is going on?
Nezuko!
Stop it!
Infuriating!
Uroki's foot!
Flesh made of the same cells as my own!
Impervious to lightning!
This little brat has good intuition!
Just now, after he burst into the room with Uroki, he was able to cut off his foot in the blink of an eye!
He can think on his feet and battle!
I can't cut off its head with my sword!
Its tongue!
Go for its tongue!
If their tongues are slashed, for some reason, these demons take longer to recover!
Yes!
I can pull it out!
I'll make you pay for that!
This is bad!
He already recovered!
It stopped!
Mezuko!
What an insolent spell!
Amazing!
Mezuko's blood is working!
Mezuko!
What an insolent spell!
Amazing!
Mezuko's blood is working!
Mezuko!
You look like you're having fun!
I!
You're avoir fun, won't ya?!
ged societies
What unbelievable pressure!
Its crushing our bodies!!
What's up?
And now, for the final blow!
Enemy attack! Demons!
Enemy attack! Protect your village!
Hurry! Hurry! Village in danger! Village in danger!
We must rush to its aid as soon as possible!
Gotta hurry! Gotta hurry! The villagers are in danger!
It's a good thing I was stationed near the swordsmith village or I never would've made it!
It must've been fake! But look!
Make haste! The village is close to destruction!
Alright! I'm going to give it my all!
To be my loved!
We've been 찾ing for the past when we were looking at them Babylaughing
and so don't dare they wouldЕ been desperate for the long run!
Voluke here!
All right.
Please remember that
The
Shade
Been a while, Combine Junior and Senior High School Tales of a Demon Slayer Academy.
I'm Mitsuri Kanroji, age 19.
My dream is to bring joy to people all over the world with my paintings.
Hey, listen to me, will you?
I wonder, when will I meet the gentleman
who's going to be the one to make me happy someday?
No one's ever gonna fall in love with someone like you.
What?!
Your hair's pink, you're a voracious eater,
and you're crazy strong.
Bummer!
That's why you paint!
That's the life you're meant to live!
You're right! Painting is all I have!
The only thing I've got that can bring joy to everyone is my art!
Next time, episode five, Bright Red Sword!
But I do wish I had a boyfriend after all!